<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DAW notes 2º at a distance</title>
    <link>http://example.org/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DAW notes 2º at a distance</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>es-ES</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 23:26:37 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Theme_1_1</title>
      <link>http://example.org/en/dwes/tema_1_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 23:26:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/en/dwes/tema_1_1/</guid>
      <description>GENERAL CONCEPTS Definition of WEB development Term that defines the process of creating a website or an intranet.
In order to do this, client-side and server-side software technologies are used involving database processes with the use of a web browser to perform tasks or display information.
To develop an application or program
 You have to understand very well what you want to do You have to plan it You have to do that planning and test it   Web Application In software engineering, a web application is defined as those tools that users can use by accessing a web server through the Internet or an intranet through a browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme_1_2</title>
      <link>http://example.org/en/dwes/tema_1_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 23:26:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/en/dwes/tema_1_2/</guid>
      <description>ARCHITECTURE AND WEB TECHNOLOGY What is web architecture The ** web architecture ** is the hierarchy of information on a ** website **. Just as traditional architecture works on the structure of a construction, web architecture works on the structure of a web page and the categories that make it up for optimization for search engine positioning.
Más info  The components of a web application 1. Web server A web server is a software (program) in charge of receiving a request over the network; In a tcp / ip type network that is the one we use on the internet, the request is received using the http protocol and responding to said request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme_3</title>
      <link>http://example.org/en/dwes/tema_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 23:26:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/en/dwes/tema_3/</guid>
      <description>LANGUAGE PHP What is php (PHP acronym: Hypertext Preprocessor) It is an open source language.
Very popular (could we think of a standard?), A large support community on the internet that contributes, collaborates and solves doubts.
Especially suitable for web development (It can be used as a desktop language, but it is not its main purpose).
Currently version 7.4.3 is updated on 9/23/2021, it is considered the stable version, and version 8.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
